"use strict"


// **************HAUNTED MANSION TRIVIA  Q/A BEGINNER **************************
//     Be sure to enter correctAnswer based on index # in the array
var questions = [{
    question: "How many ghosts are there in the Haunted Mansion?",
    choices: ["A) about a dozen", "B) 999", "C) 13", "D) 666"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "What are the Omnimover vehicles called which transport you through the ride?",
    choices: ["A) Casket Cars", "B)  Haunted Hearses", "C) Doom Buggies", "D) Death Traps"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "What is the name of the Disneyland Paris version of the Haunted Mansion?",
    choices: ["A) Phantom Manor", "B) Chamber of Chills", "C) Haunt of Horror", "D) House of Mystery"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "During the Halloween and Christmas seasons, who takes over the Haunted Mansion?",
    choices: ["A) The Headless Horseman", "B) An elf named Goofy", "C) Jack Skellington", "D) Dr Syn, the Scarecrow"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "What is the name of the medium in the Seance Room?",
    choices: ["A) Jennifer Tilley", "B) Madame Leota", "C) Maleficent", "D) Lady De Vil"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "The pipe organ is a replica of the pipe organ from which Disney movie?",
    choices: ["A) Lady and the Tramp", "B) Cinderella", "C) Steamboat Willie", "D) 20,000 Leauges Under the Sea"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "Which Disney character has a tombstone in the pet cemetery outside the mansion?",
    choices: ["A) J. Thaddeus Toad", "B) Pluto", "C) Chip and Dale", "D) Gunpowder, Ichabod's horse"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "What is the name of the Hong Kong Disneyland version of the Haunted Mansion??",
    choices: ["A) Donald's Dungeon", "B) The Crypt", "C) Castle Doom", "D) Mystic Manor"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What are the names of the 3 hitchhiking ghosts?",
    choices: ["A) Spooky, Booky & Pooky", "B) Toad, Rat & Mole", "C) Gus, Ezra & Phineas", "D) Huey, Duey & Louie"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "The voice of the Ghost Host also voice what Disney character?",
    choices: ["A) Prof. Ludwig von Drake", "B) Dumbo", "C) Tick Tock, the Crock", "D) Maximus"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}];
